Anthony F. C. Wallace Papers 1920-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.64a
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Research Notes and Drafts, 23 lin. feet (Box 24-73)
  - D. Rockdale, 1971-1995; 8 linear feet
    - Subseries 4. Finances
      - Expenses, 1972-1976; 20 items
      - Leave of Absence, 1971-1972; 19 items
      - National Science Foundation Application, 1977-1978; 67 items
      - National Science Foundation Budget, 1972-1973; 53 items
      - National Science Foundation Budget, 1973-1974; 65 items
      - National Science Foundation Budget, 1974-1975; 46 items
      - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1972; 99 items
      - National Science Foundation Supplemental Request, 1975-1976; 28 items
      - Personnel, 1972-1976; 40 items
      - Research Administration Memos, 1974-1976; 15 items
      - Rockefeller Foundation Application, 1975-1976; 74 items
      - Work-Study Students, 1973-1976; 39 items
    - Subseries 5. Student Seminar Papers
      - Bartovics, Albert F.--Archaeology of Daniels' Village (prospectus), 1973-1974; 17 items
      - Becker, Marshall Joseph
      - Behnke, Michael C.--The Anti-Masonic Monument, 1827-1840; 23 items
      - Bromberg, JoAnn--Dissertation Proposal, 4 items
      - Coleman, Michael C.--Christianizing and Americanizing the Nez Perce: Sue L. McBeth and her Attitudes to the Indians, 1975; 1 vol.
      - Gerdes, John F.--Bibliography on the Nature and Application of Models in Anthropology, 8 items
      - Gerdes, John F.--Marxian Man: Marx's View of Human Nature, 39 items
      - Gilmore, David D.--Data on Public Activities of Mill Owners, 1972; 52 items
      - Horwitz, Richard P.--Dissertation Introduction (two copies), 1973; 16 items
      - Horwitz, Richard P.--Society and Culture in a Nineteenth Century Community: Winthrop, Maine, 1830-1850 (dissertation introduction), 1972-1973; 29 items
      - Horwitz, Richard--Lowell Boardinghouse, 1971, 1973; 43 items
      - Hsu-Balzer, Eileen--Japanese Professional Women, 1972; 35 items
      - Kasserman, David--American Merchant Bibliography, 1972; 21 items
      - Kasserman, David--Daniel Lammot, 7 items
      - Kasserman, David--Dissertation Proposal, 35 items
      - Kasserman, David--T.W. Dyott and Industrial Democracy, 1970; 28 items
      - King, Robert--Cultural Innovation that Failed: The Rise and Fall of Industrial Democracy (dissertation proposal), 1975; 34 items
      - Lemieux, Christine--Living to Die: Rite of Passage Concerning Dying in Southeastern Pennsylvania, 1790-1860, 1972; 54 items
      - Lesnich ---Photocopies of Articles on Early Pennsylvania Education, 41 items
      - Lott, Steve--Slavery (Lott's notes; intro to Lott's "Industrialization and the Black Population in S.E. Penna., 1780-1840; and photocopy of Joseph E. Walker's "A Comparison of Negro and White Labor in a Charcoal Iron Community.", n.d., 1972; 61 items
      - Marx, Sandy--Literary Values of Chester and Delaware Counties (paper and notes), 1790-1850; 118 items
      - Ostrach, Stefan A.--John P. Crozier's Religious World View: A Study in Legitimation, 1973; 62 items
      - Ostrach, Stefan A.--Lowell: A Study in the Rationalization of the Industrial System, 1971; 26 items
      - Robison, Janet McClintock--An Ethnography of Medical Practice, Chester County, Pennsylvania, 1790-1861 (dissertation proposal), 1972-1973; 99 items
      - Robison, Janet McClintock--Dissertation Proposal and Conclusion, 1973; 29 items
      - Sanday, Peggy R. and Rae Alexander Minter--Frankford Bicentennial Project, 1975; 94 items
      - Walters, Dianne Bertoty--The Sharpless: A Study in Cousin Marriage, n.d.; 57 items
  - E. St. Clair, 1978-1999; 9 linear feet
    Materials from Anthony F.C. Wallace's research on the St. Clair, Schuylkill County area of the Pennsylvania coal region, including notes, drafts, photocopies of primary and secondary sources of material relating to Pennsylvania coal region history and detailed analyses of census data for the town of St. Clair, and papers from conferences and talks on St. Clair, Schuylkill County, industrialization, and the role of the hero, particularly as represented by the industrialist, in 19th century America.
    A valuable central resource for the study of Pennsylvania coal region history, with copies of rare items from repositories and libraries throughout Pennsylvania, the St. Clair subseries contains a wealth of material on coal mining, coal miners and labor organizations, Schuylkill County and Pennsylvania coal region history and the Molly Maguire crimes and trials. In addition to photocopies of most major 19th and 20th century sources on coal region history, arranged by author, the series contains primary source materials culled from several area repositories. These include deeds, correspondence, and other materials from Pennsylvania families as the Wetherills, Careys, and others influential in coal region history as well as notes and correspondence relating to the Pinkerton National Detective Agency's investigation of the Molly Maguires.
    The St. Clair subseries also includes three linear feet of photocopies of Miners' Journal newspaper articles from 1830 to 1878, which Wallace and his wife Betty extracted and arranged by subject, thereby creating an index of sorts for a publication that has no known index.
    Series III, Notecards, contains additional information on bibliographic sources for St. Clair, census data on St. Clair families, notes on prominent Schuylkill County individuals, and an alphabetical card file of miners injured and killed, which provides a less time-consuming alternative to researching the chronologically-arranged state mine accident reports for St. Clair. Series XI, Photographs, includes over 100 photo reproductions of 19th century prints and photographs depicting coal mining and the Pennsylvania coal region from the Historical Society of Schuylkill County.
    - Subseries 1. Published Primary Sources
      - Addis, John -- Crawshay Dynasty, 1957; 33 items
      - Allen, John Scott, 1925- -- 1712 and other Newcomen Engines of the Earls of Dudley, 1965; 33 items
      - Allen, John Scott, 1925- -- Introduction of the Newcomen Engine 1710-1733, 24 items
      - Appadurai, Arjun -- Culture and Consumption in an Indian Peasant Community (proposal to National Science Foundatuion), 1980; 16 items
      - Appleton's Mechanics Magazine--Notes, 1851; 1 item
      - Arensberg, Conrad Maynadier -- Irish Countryman; an Anthropological Study, 1937; 11 items
      - Ashton, T.S. and Sykes, Joseph -- Coal Industry of the Eighteenth Century, 1929; 7 items
      - Ashton, T.S. -- Discoveries of the Darbys of Coalbrookdale, 1924; 6 items
      - Aurand, Harold and William Gudelunas -- Mythical Qualities of Molly Maguire, 1982; 8 items
      - Aurand, Harold W. -- Anthracite Miner--An Occupational Analysis, 1980; 6 items
      - Aurand, Harold W. -- Anthracite Strike of 1887-1888, 9 items
      - Aurand, Harold W. -- Diversifying the Economy of the Anthracite Regions, 1880-1900, 1970; 4 items
      - Aurand, Harold W. -- From the Molly Maguires to the United Mine Workers--Notes, 4 items
      - Aurand, Harold W. -- Workingmen's Benevolent Association, 9 items
      - Baer, Christopher T. -- Constraints and Transport in the Coal Trade, 1800-1855, 1981; 12 items
      - Baer, Christopher T. -- Miner as Market Victim, 1840-1860, 1979; 26 items
      - Barone, Deborah -- Study of Domestic Cast Iron Articles Produced at Colebrookdale Furnace, Berks County, PA, 1735-1751, 1980; 33 items
      - Bell, I. Lowthian (Isaac Lowthian), 1816-1904 -- Notes of a Visit to Coal- and Iron-Mines and Ironworks in the United States, 1875; 36 items
      - Berthoff, Rowland, 1921- -- Social Order of the Anthracite Region, 1825-1902, 15 items
      - Bining, Arthur Cecil, 1893-1957 -- Rise of Iron Manufacture in Western Pennsylvania, 1933; 12 items
      - Black, Max, 1909- -- Making Intelligent Choices: How Useful is Decision Theory?, 1984; 1 item
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- Coal Regions of Pennsylvania, 1848; 25 items
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- Coal and Coal Oil, 1865; 9 items
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- Coal and the Coal-Mines of Pennsylvania, 1857; 14 items
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- Coal Regions of Pennsylvania, Being a General, Geological, Historical and Statistical Review of the Anthracite Coal Districts, 1848; 39 items
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- Coal, and the Coal Trade. A Series of Letters on the Origin of Coal and Oil Springs, 1862; 26 items
      - Bowen, Eli, b. 1824 -- McGinnes Theory of the Schuylkill Coal Formation, 1855; 29 items
      - Butler, Richard -- Effect of Industrial Changes on Occupational "Inheritance" in Four Pennsylvania Communities, 1948; 6 items
      - Campbell, Stuart -- Businessmen and Anthracite: Aspects of Change in the Late Nineteenth Century Anthracite Industry (excerpt), 1978; 9 items
      - Carey, Henry Charles, 1793-1879 -- Letter to Messrs. C.L. Harding, S.L. French, Geo. Bacon, Abbott Lawrence, B.X. Rotch, and Others, Stockholders in the St. Clair Coal Company of Boston, 1865; 17 items
      - Carey, Henry Charles, 1793-1879 -- Memorials, 1885-1959; 20 items
      - Carey, Henry Charles, 1793-1879 -- Miners Journal letters, 1860; 43 items
      - Carey, Henry Charles, 1793-1879 -- Works
      - Carpenter, John T. -- Ectrotic Virtues of Iodine in Variola, 1855; 27 items
      - Carpenter, John T. -- Report of the Schuylkill County Medical Society, 1868-1869; 5 items
      - Carter, Edward Carlos 1928- -- I have the Itch of Botany, of Chemistry, of Mathematics strong upon me: the Science of Benjamin Henry Latrobe, 1984; 1 vol.
      - Casey, Robert J. (Robert Joseph), 1890-1962 -- Lackawanna Story: First Hundred Years of the Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad (excerpts), 1951
      - Chandler, Alfred Dupont -- Anthracite Coal and the Beginnings of the Industrial Revolution in the United States
      - Chandler, Alfred Dupont -- Industrial Revolutions and Institutional Arrangements, 1980; 1 item
      - Cochran, Thomas Childs, 1902- -- Frontiers of Change: Early Industrialism in America (draft of chapter 1, "Why America and and Britain?"), c. 1980; 19 items
      - Commons, John Rogers, 1862-1945, ed. -- Knights of Labor (excerpt from A Documentary History of American Industrial Society, Vol. X, Labor Movement), 1911; 10 items
      - Commonwealth versus John Kehoe (Notes), n.d.; 11 items
      - Couch, Stephen Robert -- Centralia Grant Application, c. 1982; 35 items
      - Couch, Stephen Robert -- Chronic Technical Disaster: Toward a Social Scientific Perspective, 1985; 1 item
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895 -- Biographical Notice of Franklin B. Gowen, 1890; 3 items
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895 -- Mining Legislation. A Paper Read at the General Meeting of the American Social Science Association at Philadelphia, October 25, 1870, 10 items
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895 -- New Method of Sinking Shafts, 1872; 13 items
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895 -- Secondary Technical Education. An Address Delivered Before the American Institute of Mining Engineers at their Baltimore Meeting, 1879; 7 items
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895 -- Social Science Association of Philadelphia. Papers of 1871. Boards of Conciliation and Arbitration, 14 items
      - Coxe, Eckley Brinton, 1839-1895
      - Daddow, Samuel Harries, 1827-1875 -- Coal, Iron, and Oil; or, the Practical American Miner, 1866; 438 items
      - Daddow, Samuel Harries, 1827-1875 -- Noncarra's Bad Luck, 5 items
      - Daddow, Samuel Harries, 1827-1875 -- Trevaro, and other occasional poems, written by "Alpha Lyra" [pseud.], [Place], 1853; 159 items
      - Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895 -- New text-book of geology. Designed for schools and academies (excerpt), [Place], pref. 1877; 5 items
      - Danville and Pottsville Railroad -- Report of the President and Managers of the Danville and Pottsville Rail Road Company to the Stockholders, 1839; 12 items
      - Davies, Edward J., II, 1947- -- Anthracite aristocracy: leadership and social change in the hard coal regions of northeastern Pennsylvania, 1800-1930 (Notes), 2 items
      - Davies, Edward J., II, 1947-
      - Davy, Humphry, Sir, 1788-1829 -- On the Fire Damp of Coal Mines (notes), 1816; 2 items
      - Day, Sherman, 1806-1884 -- Historical Collections of the State of Pennsylvania (excerpts), 1843; 8 items
      - Donovan, Arthur -- Carboniferous Capitalism: Excess Productive Capacity and Institutional Backwardness in the U.S. Coal Industry, 1983; 7 items
      - Eavenson, Howard Nicholas, 1873- -- First Century and a Quarter of American Coal (notes), 1942; 1 item
      - Ecenbarger, William -- John O'Hara Could Go Home Again, [Place], 1982
      - Eleutherian Mills Hagley Foundation -- Anthracite Conference, 1982; 11 items
      - Erickson, Charlotte, 1923- -- Invisible Immigrants: The Adaptation of English and Scottish Immigrants in Nineteenth Century America (excerpts), 1972; 16 items
      - Evans, Chris -- History of United Mine Workers of America from the year 1860 to 1890, 1918?-1920; 43 items
      - Faler, Paul G. (Paul Gustaf), 1940- -- Cultural Aspects of the Industrial Revolution: Lynn, Massachusetts, Shoemakers, and Industrial Morality, 1826-1860. From Labor History 15, 1974; 27 items
      - Faust, Drew Gilpin -- Rhetoric and Ritual of Agriculture in Antebellum South Carolina. Journal of Southern History, Vol. XLV, No. 4, 1979; 14 items
      - Fowler, John A. d. 1911 -- Fire Insurance Premium, 1876; 11 items
      - Fowler, John A. d. 1911 -- History of insurance in Philadelphia for two centuries (1683-1882), 1888
      - Geddes, William F., printer -- Comparative Views of the Most Important Anthracite Collieries in Pennsylvania, [Place], 1835
      - George, Henry -- Labor in Pennsylvania, North American Review, vol. 143 (1886); vol. 144 (1887), 1886-1887; 26 items
      - Government Publications--Hasse, Adelaide Rosalia, 1868-1953 -- Index of State Documents: Pennsylvania, 1919; 64 items
      - Government Publications--Packer--Report on the Coal Trade -- Packer, S.J. Report of the Committee of the Senate upon the Subject of the Coal Trade, 1834; 99 items
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania Bureau of Industrial Statistics -- Pennsylvania Bureau of Industrial Statistics. Annual Report of the Secretary of Internal Affairs of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. Industrial Statistics
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania Bureau of Statistics of Labor -- Philadelphia Social Science Association, The Census in Philadelphia, 1872-1873; 84 items
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania Bureau of Statistics of Labor -- United States Department of Energy--Historian's Office, [Place], 1979; 5 items
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania Joint Committee of the Legislature -- Report of the Joint Committee of the Legislature of Pennsylvania, Appointed to Inquire into the Affairs of the Philadelphia and Reading Coal and Iron Company and...Railroad Company, 1876
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania, House of Representatives -- Journal of House of Representatives and Journal of Senate; Acts 885 and 1327, [Place], 1866; 21 items
      - Government Publications--Pennsylvania. Senate -- Pennsylvania. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary General. Report in Relation to the Anthracite Coal Difficulties, 1871; 123 items
      - Government Publications--St. Clair Coal Company -- Answer of the St. Clair Coal Company Before the Anthracite Coal Strike Commission, 1901; 24 items
      - Government Publications--U.S. Report of U.S. Coal Commission -- United States. Coal commission. Report of the United States Coal Commission, 1925; 53 items
      - Government Publications--U.S. Report on Capital and Labor in Mining Industry -- United States. Industrial Commission. Report of the Industrial Commission on the Relations and Conditions of Capital and Labor Employed in the Mining Industry, 1901; 27 items
      - Government Publications--United States Department of Energy -- Historian's Office--Energy History Report, 1979-1980; 5 items
      - Government Publications--United States, House--Labor Troubles -- United States. Congress. House. Committee on Commerce. Labor Troubles in the Anthracite Regions of Pennsylvania, 1887-1888; 309 items
      - Grady, John -- Grant Proposals, 1981
      - Greene, Victor, 1933- -- A Study in Slavs, Strikes, and Unions: The Anthracite Strike of 1897
      - Gregory, J.W. -- Henry Darwin Rogers: An Address to the Glasgow University Geological Society, 1916; 20 items
      - Grob, Gerald N., 1931- -- Workers and Utopia. A Study of Ideological Conflict in the American Labor Movement 1865-1900 (Ch. 2 Reform Unionism: The National Labor Union), 1961; 25 items
      - Gudelunas, William A. -- Rise of the Irish Factor in Anthracite Politics, 1850-1880, 1981; 25 items
      - Haldeman, H.L. -- Chickie's Furnace, [Place], 1896; 9 items
      - Hall, J.W. -- Notes on Coalbrookdale and the Darbys, 1924; 8 items
      - Hare, Jay V. -- History of the Reading, 1909-1914; 55 items
      - Harper's Weekly -- Down among the coal mines, 1873; 6 items
      - Harper's Weekly -- Horrors of the Mine, 1873; 8 items
      - Harris, Joseph S. -- Report of Joseph S. Harris, Esq., upon the coal landsof the Philadelphia and Reading Coal and Iron Co., 1880; 32 items
      - Hart, Lane S., printer and binder -- White slaves of monopolies; or, John Fitz Patrick, the miner, soldier and workingman's friend: A history of his struggles with mine owners, corporations [etc.], 1884; 186 items
      - Hartranft, Paul Edgar -- History of the Public Schools (excerpts and notes), M.A. thesis, Pennsylvania State University, 12 items
      - Hedley, John -- A Practical Treatise on the Working and Ventilation of Coal Mines; with Suggestions for Improvements in Mining (excerpt), 1851
      - Henning, D.C. -- Early Annals of Pottsville, 1910; 28 items
      - Hewitt, Nancy A., 1951- -- An Ethnohistorical Approach to Women's Activism in Rochester, New York, 1820-1860, 1980
      - Hirsch, Mark D. (Mark David), 1910- -- Class, Ethnicity and the Irish Miners of the Lower Anthracite Region of Pennsylvania 1850-1880, 1981; 30 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Channell, G.W.--Port Carbon and Her People, 1912; 6 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Early History of Coal Mining and Mining Machinery in Schuylkill County, [Place], 1912; 22 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Eastman, Elizabeth--Early Days in Pottsville, [Place], 1911; 4 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Elssler, Ermina--History of the Henry Clay Monument, [Place], 1909; 13 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Filbert, J.H.--Joseph F. Patterson. Delivered before the Schuylkill County Historical Society, 1924; 6 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- John, J.J.--Rambles Over a King's Highway of Colonial Times, 1905; 31 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- John, J.J.--The Centre Turnpike Road: One of the Famous Old Turnpikes of Our Commonwealth, 1909; 17 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- John, J.J.--The Story About One of the First Chartered Railroads in America, [Place], 1906; 35 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Maguire, John--Early Pennsylvania Coal Mine Legislation, 2 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Newell, William H.--Legends and Traditions of Schuylkill County, [Place], 1912; 3 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Patterson, Joseph F.--Old W.B.A. Days, [Place], 1910; 31 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Patterson, Joseph F.--Reminiscences of John Maguire After Fifty Years of Mining, 1912; 43 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Patterson, Joseph--After the W.B.A., [Place], 1911; 9 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Volume I, [Place], 1907; 136 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Volume IV, [Place], 1912; 370 items
      - Historical Society of Schuylkill County Publications -- Volume V., No. 3, [Place], n.d.; 13 items
      - Homrighaus, Barbara -- Dangerous Work Must Be Done: Oral Histories of Child Labor, [Place], 1987; 1 vol.
      - Homrighaus, Barbara -- Immigration and Ethnicity in the Anthracite Region: The Peter Kowker Story, [Place], 1986-1987; 11 items
      - Horwitz, Richard P., 1949- -- Architecture and Culture: the Meaning of the Lowell Boarding House, 1973; 13 items
      - Howard, Robert A. and E. Alvin Gerhardt, Jr. -- Mary Patton, Powder Maker of the Revolution (removed for cataloguing), [Place], 1980
      - Howard, Robert A. -- A Primer on Water Turbines, n.d.; 22 items
      - Howard, Robert A. -- Gunpowder in the American Revolution (in Arms Gazette--removed for cataloguing), 1976
      - Howard, Robert A. -- Interchangeable Parts Reexamined: The Private Sector of the American Arms Industry on the Eve of the Civil War., 1978; 17 items
      - Howard, Robert A. -- Technology Outline, n.d.; 9 items
      - Howard, Robert A. -- Water Power: How it Works, 1979; 1 vol.
      - Howard, Robert A.
      - Hughes, Thomas Parke -- Bridge that Spanned the World (transcript), [Place], 1980
      - Hughes, Thomas Parke -- Convergent Themes in the History of Science, Medicine, and Technology (removed for cataloguing), 1981; 9 items
      - Humphrey, H.D. -- Historical Summary of Coal-Mine Explosions in the United States, 1810-1958 (Bulletin 586, Bureau of Mines), 1960; 15 items
      - Insurance -- Insurance Yearbook for 1874 (excerpt), [Place], 2 items
      - Insurance -- Annual Report of the Committee on Adjustments and Statistics of the National Board of Fire Underwriters, 1873-1874; 63 items
      - Insurance -- Binney, Horace--Address (from Centennial Meeting of the Philadelphia Contributorship for the Insurance of Houses from Loss by Fire, 1852; 22 items
      - Insurance -- Miners' Journal Advertisements, 1860-1867; 4 items
      - Itter, William A. -- Early Labor Troubles in the Schuylkill Anthracite District. (Pennsylvania History, vol. 1), 1934; 5 items
      - Jenkins, Rhys -- A Sketch of the Industrial History of the Coalbrookdale District, 1924; 3 items
      - Jenkins, Rhys -- Iron-making in the Forest of Dean, 1925; 24 items
      - John, A.H. -- Minutes Relating to Messrs. Samuel Walker and Co. Rotherham, Iron Founders and Steel Refiners, 1741-1829 and Messrs. Walkers, Parker, and Co. Lead Manufacturers, 1788-1893, 1951; 9 items
      - Johnson, Mary -- Ennui as a Force in History (panel proposal for Fifth Berkshire Conference on Women's History), c. 1980-1981; 6 items
      - Johnson, Mary -- Madame E.I. du Pont and Madame Victorine du Pont Bauduy, The First Mistresses of Eleutherian Mills: Models of Domesticity in the Brandywine Valley during the Antebellum Era, 1981; 37 items
      - Johnson, Mary -- Servant Problem in the Brandywine Valley in the Antebellum Era, 1981; 43 items
      - Johnson, Walter R. (Walter Rogers), 1794-1852 -- Notes on the Use of Anthracite in the Manufacture of Iron with Some Remarks on its Evaporating Power, 1841; 30 items
      - Jordan, William M. -- Geology and the Industrial-Transportation Revolution in Early to Mid Nineteenth-Century Pennsylvania, 1979; 8 items
      - Journal of the Franklin Institute -- Notes and Articles on Mining, [Place], 1867, 1872; 48 items
      - Kaminsky, John -- Carpatho-Slav Culture and Culture Change in St. Clair, Pennsylvania, 1951; 88 items